We're going to take a different approach to start this section.
Instead of me talking about a bunch of topics and then give you an exercise, we're going to
start with an exercise. So I want you to spend 15-20
minutes and build this pagination component. So,
start by thinking about the interface of this component, what data
does this component need, what are the events it's going to raise?
Think about this and then start implementing this component. Now
in terms of the UI, this is a bootstrap pagination component,
so on bootstrap documentation if you search
for pagination, you can see a basic
pagination component, don't worry about the previous and next buttons,
just focus on the page numbers. So this is the mark up
that you need to return from your pagination component. So go ahead and
build this, when you are done, come back and see my solution.